[
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "ho_ey",
      "options": ["A", "N", "B"],
      "answer": "N"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "c_t",
      "options": ["A", "U", "I"],
      "answer": "A"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "su_",
      "options": ["P", "N", "M"],
      "answer": "N"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "pl_nt",
      "options": ["A", "E", "O"],
      "answer": "A"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "dr_m",
      "options": ["I", "A", "E"],
      "answer": "E"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "f_ox",
      "options": ["I", "L", "R"],
      "answer": "R"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "bo_k",
      "options": ["A", "O", "U"],
      "answer": "O"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "st_r",
      "options": ["A", "O", "E"],
      "answer": "A"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "cl_wn",
      "options": ["A", "O", "I"],
      "answer": "O"
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "fr_g",
      "options": ["A", "O", "I"],
      "answer": "O"
    }
]
